<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Blog on </title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/portfolio/en/blog/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Blog on </description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 14:38:33 +0200</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/portfolio/en/blog/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Exploring Students’ and Teachers’ Perspectives in AI-supported Classrooms</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/portfolio/en/blog/masterthesis/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Sep 2024 14:38:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/portfolio/en/blog/masterthesis/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;masterthesis-for-the-attainment-of-the-degree-master-of-science-msc&#34;&gt;Masterthesis for the Attainment of the Degree Master of Science (M.Sc.)&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;p&gt;Supervisor: Prof. Dr. Tomohiro Nagashima &amp;amp; Dr. Man Su&lt;/p&gt;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;display: flex; align-items: flex-start; gap: 20px; flex-wrap: wrap;&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;!-- Text links --&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div style=&#34;flex: 2; min-width: 250px;&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;p&gt;&#xA;      The growing integration of AI-powered technologies in classrooms is reshaping the roles of students and teachers, especially regarding student agency and autonomy. We conducted a speed-dating interview study with 16 secondary school students and 15 teachers in Germany to explore where their perceptions and preferences regarding AI use align or diverge. Using storyboards that illustrated a spectrum from full learner control to full AI control, both groups expressed shared views on appropriate AI use, but also differed in how they envisioned AI support in the classroom. The results emphasize the critical role of the student-teacher relationship in shaping attitudes toward AI systems. By including both student and teacher voices, this study aims to foster a more nuanced understanding of the balance between human agency and AI automation in education.&#xA;    &lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>From Crisi to Confidence: An Intro intro Replication Crisis and Open Science</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/portfolio/en/blog/replicationcrisis/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 28 May 2023 14:38:33 +0200</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/portfolio/en/blog/replicationcrisis/</guid>
      <description>&lt;h1 id=&#34;interactive-learning-session-on-the-replication-crisis&#34;&gt;Interactive Learning Session on the Replication Crisis&lt;/h1&gt;&#xA;&lt;div style=&#34;display: flex; align-items: flex-start; gap: 20px; flex-wrap: wrap;&#34;&gt;&#xA;  &lt;!-- Text links --&gt;&#xA;  &lt;div style=&#34;flex: 2; min-width: 250px;&#34;&gt;&#xA;    &lt;p&gt;&#xA;    Developed in a group project for the Instructional Design II course in the Master&#39;s program Educational Technology, this learning unit introduces learners to the replication crisis in empirical research using Articulate Storyline 360. The unit explores why the replicability of scientific findings is crucial for the relevance and generalizability of results (Open Science Collaboration, 2015), and emphasizes how research decisions impact outcome quality (Diener &amp; Biswas-Diener, 2023). &lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
